const qBank = [
    {
        id: 1,
        question: "3 + 5 =",
        options: ["3", "10", "8", "-2"],
        answer: "8"
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        question: "9 + 4 =",
        options: ["10", "13", "14", "11"],
        answer: "13"
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        question: "The protagonist of the jujutsu kaisen?",
        options: ["Yuji Itadori", "Satoru Gojo", "Sukuna Ryomen", "Yuta Okkotsu"],
        answer: "Yuji Itadori"
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        question: "How many seasons in jujutsu kaisen?",
        options: ["3", "1", "4", "1"],
        answer: "1"
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        question: "What time of day is 15:00?",
        options: ["morning", "day", "evening", "night"],
        answer: "8"
    },
    {
        id: 6,
        question: "When do people usually eat soup?",
        options: ["breakfast", "brunch", "dinner", "supper"],
        answer: "dinner"
    },
    {
        id: 7,
        question: "The main sport in Brazil?",
        options: ["volleyball", "basketball", "football", "hockey"],
        answer: "football"
    },
    {
        id: 8,
        question: "What is the currency in Germany?",
        options: ["dollar", "Euro", "ruble", "yuan"],
        answer: "Euro"
    },
    {
        id: 9,
        question: "Favorite vegetable in Belarus?",
        options: ["cucumber", "tomato", "potato", "carrot"],
        answer: "potato"
    },
    {
        id: 10,
        question: "When is the harvest?",
        options: ["summer", "autumn", "winter", "spring"],
        answer: "autumn"
    },
]

export default qBank;